<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bored Electron</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bored Electron</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright notice</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:53:56 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Embedded Systems with CAN Message Multiplexing in C</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/canmsg_mux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/canmsg_mux/</guid>
      <description>In the world of embedded systems, particularly in automotive applications, the Controller Area Network (CAN) protocol is a crucial backbone for communication between Electronic Control Units (ECUs). A powerful technique used to manage data efficiently on the CAN bus is multiplexing.&#xA;Multiplexing allows a single CAN message to carry data for multiple different parameters.&#xA;This blog post explores an optimized C programming approach to process these multiplexed messages. Instead of using verbose if-else or switch statements, we will demonstrate how to use pointers and structures to create a more compact, scalable, and efficient solution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 23:51:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am Vallabh.&#xA;I am an engineer. I work on embedded automotive projects. I use C all the time and am flexible enough to learn python.&#xA;This is my blog - The Siliconomist. I write about tech, science and any stuff that grabs my attention. I also have my trip photos in my gallery.&#xA;Currently this static site is hosted using hugo, using the ink-theme by knadh. I plan to improve the theme and add updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:32:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/gallery/</guid>
      <description>My trek to KonKanKada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/first_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:57:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/first_post/</guid>
      <description>Hi all. This is my first post!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
